[
  {
    "question" : "If you drink sprite right after eating a banana you will throw up",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "I sit next to liam in comp sci",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Mt everest is 15,000 meters tall",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "Eliud Kipchoge ran 1:59:40 for the Marathon on October 12th 2019",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Lots of students are stressed due to a large workload, phones, and a lack of sleep, but Mr Shorr's students are fine",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Liam does not enjoy running",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Me and Liam made Galaga for our final project last year",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "10832482366 * 473027846382456 - 97326426 * 4327^-74368463756 = 42",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Based off of this political cartoon, how many years will it be until the airspeed velocity of Liam's bed reaches purple?",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "The answer is false",
    "answer" : true
  }

]